# ALYSSA BEATRICE **DIOKNO**

• Cavite, PH

**\** 0956 749 4959

■ dioknobea@gmail.com

in linkedin.com/in/dioknobea

# **OBJECTIVE**

Looking to obtain an internship position to acquire extensive knowledge and experience on the field, in fulfillment of course requirements. Comes with the ability to work and learn at the same time.

## **ABOUT ME**

A 3rd year BS Computer Science student in University of the Philippines Diliman. Demonstrates a resourceful approach in analyzing and solving problems. A quick learner, team player, and is capable of adapting to many situations. Has experience in data analysis and front-end development.

## **EXPERIENCE**

## Front-end Developer

September 2021 - Present

University of the Philippines Diliman

Currently in charge with building the front-end of a website for a Software Engineering course.

#### Research Intern

July 2021 - August 2021

System Modeling and Simulation Laboratory - UP Department of Computer Science

Worked on simulations of school opening scenarios in NCR using a COVID-19 agent-based model.

#### Research Intern

July 2021 - August 2021

University of San Agustin - Center for Informatics

Received training in data visualization and analysis of COVID-19 data with Python and Tableau.

## **EDUCATION**

## **B.S. in Computer Science**

August 2019 - Present University of the Philippines Diliman

## High School Diploma

June 2013 - April 2019

Rogationist College - Silang, Cavite

# **RELEVANT COURSEWORK**

- Data Structures and Algorithms
- Computer Organization and Architecture
- Computer Programming
- · Artificial Intelligence
- Software Engineering
- Data Science

# **SKILLS**

- Python
- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- C